You three, don't take another step!
Step away from the water!
Don't try to pull anything on us.
I know one of you did this!
Did what?
The one who killed the guard
and tried to drown us!
I know it's one of you!
We really need to figure out who snuck in,
or we're all toast!
What are you talking about?
I said don't move.
Atroe said she didn't recognize you.
What about you two?
Do you recall seeing her from the start?
I don't recall your faces either.
Come on, you know I've been here
right from the start.
I don't remember your face.
Hey!
No one remembers you either, bitch.
I'm the one who called help
over the radio just now.
You could be trying to trick us.
Wait a second.
You, with the black hair.
You've got a nosebleed.
What the…
I couldn't see well, but…
Ermes, when I punched
the enemy Stand earlier,
someone almost collapsed.
Step back.
Stand away from the water.
Hold on, you've got it all wrong!
This bitch punched my face just now!
Look at her! She's bleeding too.
What the hell?
Her tooth scratched my arm!
I was definitely here
right from the start.
The culprit is one of these two!
Listen, I remember what happened
with that crocodile warden!
You're the one who caused a scene!
She did do that.
You guys are just as suspicious…
Jolyne!
Was it this bitch that attacked us?
How did you figure it out?
Well, to be honest,
I have no clue who the killer is.
So I'll just beat you all up!
You…
You bitch!
She's…
I was going to finish you off
one by one in the water.
Who would've guessed
she had a thread ability
and would survive the attack?
Just what are these people?
They all killed him?
What's going on?
Who's the actual Stand User?
You're wrong.
One Stand User
for each Stand ability.
The women who were here from the start
were the black-haired
and the shaved-head one.
I finished them off
because they approached the tractor.
I then took over their body and mind.
This body, I created it…
using the missing inmates' flesh!
EPISODE 8: F.F.
The black sludge
is gathering from those two.
The divided parts of me
have now formed into one.
For the ability and the intellect
Pale Snake's discs have enabled me,
I will protect myself at any cost.
It is my duty
to eliminate those
who approach the storage shed.
Dammit.
Where is the Stand User?
You're misunderstanding it, Ermes.
He is the Stand User himself.
What?
He is an organism.
He is a living creature
who received life and power
through the discs.
The guard of the discs wasn't human.
A living creature?
You mean, that conglomeration
of those tiny things?
It must be using the water
in the bodies of its victims
to move on land and guard the shed.
It stays on land
by dividing and multiplying.
However, as a car needs gasoline,
it needs water to live.
To acquire the discs,
we need to keep this creature
out of the water and defeat it!
But Jolyne,
how can a tiny flea-like thing talk?
F.F.
Call me by my name!
An astronomer named Fred Hoyle once said,
"It is probabilistically wrong to assume
that life was born spontaneously on Earth.
The power of intellect
already existed in this universe,
and it created the origin of life."
Meaning intellect existed
long before the Big Bang,
and all substances and organisms
already possessed intellect.
What is he blabbering on about?
He's trying to say that humans
are not the only ones with intellect.
Even plankton have memory--
I told you to call me F.F.!
I am a being
of superior intellect than you!
This is bad.
He's trying to hide the discs
before we can get to them.
If he buries them underground,
we'll never be able to find them!
Jolyne, we're in trouble here.
Look behind you.
That's the creature
that attacked us from the water.
He's trying to drag the guard's body.
Remember the bracelet?
We must stay within 50 meters of it.
It's over, Jolyne.
Let's give up on the discs.
We must get the guard's body!
The bracelet will explode.
I'll leave the bracelet to you, Ermes.
What?
While I run 50 meters,
you protect the guard's body
and drag it within my safety range!
That's the only way!
Hey, I said wait!
What a woman.
She's nuts!
Why would she leave that to me?
But, dammit.
If it takes the guard's body,
then it's over for Jolyne and me.
I need to act now!
I did it, dammit.
But I'll never use the sticker
like this ever again.
I'll never create another arm for myself.
This will hurt, dammit.
I just have to carry him
within 50 meters of the shed…
Water.
You little worm!
That holler…
You think you've won?
This is the corpse
your original dried out to the bone.
This corpse has zero moisture.
My sticker has split it into two.
When I remove the sticker…
You sure absorb water like a tampon.
Or should I say,
a drop of water in a desert?
Shut up! You're in the way!
Scram!
Jolyne.
We need to dehydrate it.
That's the only way to win
against these tiny bastards.
You made it in time.
Either way, I will kill you two.
I was planning to ask you questions
after hiding these discs.
But very well.
Let me ask you this.
Will you jump into the puddle?
Or will you try to run?
Which death do you prefer?
I have questions as well.
The one who knows what you are.
Is it Pale Snake?
Also,
what is his aim and reason
for collecting the discs?
How interesting.
I understand the logic
behind an offensive defense.
And fighting to protect your friends,
I can't relate,
but it's also within reason.
However, I don't understand
why you'd come here to die.
Well, Pale Snake, was it?
Who knows? I've never seen him.
You thought I was distracted, you fool?
These puddles are already a part of me!
Did you plan to break this bag of flour
and absorb water?
Either way,
I fully understand my ability
and have created
the optimal environment for myself.
It may not be so bad
to use your body as a host for a while.
No.
You've already lost.
This environment you've created
by spilling water everywhere…
It will lead to your defeat.
You didn't even hear me
start the tractor using my threads.
The sound was drowned by the water.
You got distracted with killing me.
And now, you've failed to guard the discs.
You… Damn you!
I cannot allow you to have them!
Those discs are my…
The dirt in the field
is much softer than that of the wetlands.
Water is getting absorbed from its body.
And there won't be water at the end point!
I won't let you lay
a single finger on those discs--
Jolyne won this battle of wits.
The discs don't belong to you anymore.
You're finished!
Dry up and become feed for the crops!
Jolyne.
Jolyne, what the hell are you doing?
I'll give it water.
Let's just say,
I'm saving it.
What?
F.F.
He wasn't guarding the discs
out of loyalty to Pale Snake.
I know that now.
Though it knows its body will wither away,
it chased after the discs.
It was guarding the discs
to protect its own existence.
The discs gave it ability and intellect.
It risked his life for the gratitude
it has, to be able to exist.
It could care less about Pale Snake.
Hey, you want to save it?
It killed five people!
And it's literally not human!
If it's not human,
then it doesn't understand evil.
Pale Snake is the evil one.
Pale Snake only gave it the information
that would allow him to take advantage.
What?
And I have another reason
for saving its life.
I made a deal with you.
These discs, I want you to keep them safe.
But do it for us.
Keep them out of Pale Snake's hands.
My intention is not to take
those discs from you.
I only want my father's discs back.
And I want to know
what Pale Snake is scheming to do.
Well? Will you help us?
But no more killing humans.
Dammit.
You really are something.
I don't quite understand your feelings,
but I no longer feel like fighting.
And, I have lost… completely.
DISC OBTAINED
SUNBURN (NO CORPSE)
SHAVED-HEAD (NO CORPSE)
BLACK-HAIRED (BONE-DRY CORPSE)
ATROE (DEATH FROM EXPLOSION)
STAND NAME: F.F.
STAND MASTER: F.F.
So the discs really
were stored in the tire!
We finally found them!
This is Star Platinum!
Jolyne!
Are you okay? Hey!
I have no doubt about it.
This is Star Platinum's disc.
My father, Jotaro Kujo,
can be resuscitated with it.
It's finally in my hand!
But I don't see his memory disc.
Where could it be?
Hey.
If I jump out of that window,
do you think I'll die?
Come on, it's just me.
It's me!
F.F., just call me that.
I recovered whatever remained of her.
I wore another inmate's bracelet.
I want to use this body
as a host for a while.
This hand is useless, though.
Take over her life?
You mean,
you'll live in her cell as a prisoner?
Jolyne,
I want to protect you.
According to the memory in this body,
her name is Atroe.
Inmate number FE39423.
Her childhood dream was to get kidnapped.
But when she grew up,
she ended up kidnapping a child.
She wasn't after the ransom.
She doesn't know why she did it.
What the…
Your arms are bleeding.
Do they hurt?
But I can't heal them.
-What the hell?
-Gross!
Water!
You might want to wait
on going inside the prison.
How about practicing
drinking from a cup first?
A cup?
That's a piece of cake!
Drinking from a cup is nothing.
Gross.
Hey, I wanted to ask you about Pale Snake.
Does he come to this shed often?
No, he barely swings by.
I've never seen his user either.
The discs stored here
are the ones he doesn't use.
No matter how strong the Stand,
the body rejects the disc
if you're incompatible.
So all the discs are
the ones he cannot use.
He must have another hiding place
for the important ones.
And that's why
the memory disc you're seeking
isn't in this pile.
What he really wanted from your father
wasn't an invincible Stand ability
but his memory.
It must be one hell of a secret.
Secret…
The guards are here.
What are you going to do, Jolyne?
You have the Star Platinum disc.
My next step
is to deliver this to the foundation
treating my father.
If I don't resuscitate him soon,
his body will begin to rot.
And I'll find his memory disc
no matter what it takes.
Deliver it outside of this prison.
It's harder to get things
out of here than in.
And the guards will soon
conduct a body check.
Let me see that disc for a sec.
I'll just make my boobs a bit bigger.
Ta-da.
F.F., raise your hands or you'll get shot.
Ermes, you too.
The guard was attacked by a crocodile.
We saved him.
We don't know what happened
to the other inmates.
That's the story we're sticking to, okay?
She was just bait.
Jolyne was just bait to attract Jotaro.
I believed she would be harmless.
Jolyne Cujoh.
Did she defeat the guard
by herself and take the discs?
Could it be that the surviving inmates
aided Jolyne?
Hey, it's already sundown.
You must return to the prison soon.
Are you that worried
about the missing inmates,
Father Pucchi?
A moment, please.
I will be staying here
until I give the sacrament on Sunday.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter